A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Communications, SG 2, Series 5 FA481
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Communications, 5
  - Publications, 5
    - Rural Hospital Program - By-Laws-Rules and Regulations - Pittsfield, Illinois, Ada, Oklahoma, Rochester, New York, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 203)
    - Public Health Nursing Care of the Sick, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 204)
    - Southside Community Hospital - Farmville Virginia - Hospital By-Laws, Rules and Regulations, 1944, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 205)
    - Medicine and the Neuroses - Report of the Hershey Conference on Psychiatric Rehabilitation, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 206)
    - Rural Hospital Program - By-Laws, Rules and Regulations - Lancaster, SC, Provo, Utah, Bristol, Virginia-Tennessee, 1933, 1942, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 207)
    - Rural Hospital Program - By-Laws - Community Hospital Corporation - Glasgow, Kentucky, 1946 March 7 (Box 31, Folder 208)
    - Medical Research Review 1936-1944, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 209)
    - The Regional Hospital Plan - The Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 210)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Publications, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 211)
    - Reginal Bulletin - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals, Inc., 1947 April 1 (Box 31, Folder 212)
    - Education for the Health Services in the State of Florida, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 213)
    - The Economy Shop Aids the Community Hospital - Tenth Annual Benifits Banquet, 1949 Feb. 2 (Box 31, Folder 214)
    - The Destruction of the Muller-Lyer Illusion in Repeated Trials - I. An Examination of two Theories II. Satiation Patterns and Memory Traces - Reprints - Journal of Experimental Psychology, 1950 April & June (Box 31, Folder 215)
    - Maternity Care in Two Counties Gibson County Tennessee, Pike County, Mississippi, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 216)
    - Medical Research Review, 1944-1951 (Box 32, Folder 218, Folder 217)
    - Medical Research Review, 1952-1958 (Box 32, Folder 219, Folder 220)
    - Minute - Memorium - Adapted by the Board of Directors - Barry Congar Smith, 1952 Nov. 20 (Box 32, Folder 221)
    - Minute Mermorium - Adopted by the Board of Directors - Geddes Smith, 1953 Nov. 12 (Box 32, Folder 222)
    - Group Practice with Branch Centers in a Rural County - Reprint - New England Journal of Medicine, 1953 March 9 (Box 32, Folder 223)
    - On the Scientific Status of Psychoanalysis - Reprint - from the Scientific Monthly, 1954 Nov. (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - Before the Special Committee to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations - 83rd Congress Statement of the Rockefeller Foundation and the General Education Board, 1954 Aug. 3 (Box 32, Folder 225)
    - Currents of the Auditory Cortex in the Cat and Currents of the Human Auditory Cotex, 1955 April (Box 32, Folder 226)
    - Experience with Home Care for Cardiac Patients - Reprint - American Journal of Public Health, 1955 April (Box 32, Folder 227)
    - Teaching of Growth and Development and Human Ecology at the Boston City Hospital - Reprint - The Boston Medical Quarterly, 1955 Sept. (Box 32, Folder 228)
    - A Golden Opportunity ...to Share In America's Health - Stanford Medical Center Fund, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 229)
    - Commonwealth Fund Fellowships - To Graduates of the Universities of the United Kingdom - A Review 1925-1955, 1957 April (Box 32, Folder 230)
    - Annual Report of Director of Health Studies, 1956 July 1 - 1957 June 30 (Box 32, Folder 231)
    - Review of Commonwealth Fund - Experiments in Medical Education, Part I, 1959 April 21 (Box 33, Folder 232)
    - Review of Commonwealth Fund - Experiments in Medical Education, Part II, 1958 Oct. 8 (Box 33, Folder 233)
    - 87th Congress, 1st Session H.R. 4222, 1961 Feb. 13 (Box 33, Folder 234)
    - In Memoriam - Harry P. Davison, 1898 April 3 - 1961 July 2 (Box 33, Folder 235)
    - Topics of Current Medical Interest - Arizona Medical School Study in Retrospect, 1962 July (Box 33, Folder 236)
    - Emerging Patterns of American Medicine - Columbia University, 1964 May 13 (Box 33, Folder 237)
    - The Mind of Social Work, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 238)
    - 89th Congress, 1st, Session H.R. 9256, 1965 June 21 (Box 33, Folder 239)
    - 89th Congress, 2nd Session H.R. 12453, 1966 Feb. 2 (Box 33, Folder 240)
    - Bulletin of the Post-Grauate Committee in Medicine - University of Sidney, 1966 March (Box 33, Folder 241)
    - The Education of Public Health Personnel - Report of the Joint Committee on the Study of Education for Public Health - A Pilot Study, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 242)
    - Task Force on Environmental Health - Changing Environmental Hazards - Challenges to Community Health, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 243)
    - West Virgina's Boldest Educational Experiment - A Report to the People of Alderson-Broaddus College 1956-1966, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 244)
    - Advances in Planned Parenthood - Volume III, 1967 April 3-4 (Box 33, Folder 245)
    - The Organization of Health Services in Eastern Europe - Report of a Study in Czechoslovakia, Hungary, and Poland, Spring 1967 - Reprint - Medical Care, 1968 July-Aug. (Box 33, Folder 246)
    - Bostonia - Boston University Alumni Magazine, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 247)
    - Comprehensive Community Health Services for N.Y.C. - Report of the Commission on the Delivery of Personal Health Services, 968 (Box 33, Folder 248)
    - Count Your Blessings, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 249)
    - Letters from Exeter - The Harkness Plan - Classroom and Will it Survive?, 1967 Feb. & 1980 (Box 33, Folder 250)
    - Clinical Teaching and Health Care Systems - Models and Evaluation - A Report to the Commonwealth Fund, 1969 June (Box 34, Folder 251)
    - The Code of Science Analysis anf Reflections on its Future - Columbia University, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 252)
    - A Rededication - Medical Center of the American University of Beirut, 1970 June 26 (Box 34, Folder 253)
    - Third Men in the Arenas of Conflict - An Assessment ... American Arbitration Asso., 1970 Nov. (Box 34, Folder 254)
    - Role of the Servant Essays - Greenleaf, Robert K., 1970-1975 (Box 34, Folder 255)
    - Report of The Chapman Task Force - Boston University Medical Center, 1971 March (Box 34, Folder 256)
    - Meeting Health Manpower Needs Through more Effective Use of Allied Health Workers, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 257)
    - Handbook on U.S. Study for Foreign Nationals - Institute of International Education, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 258)
    - The American College of Physicians - Convocation Program, 1973 April 13 (Box 34, Folder 259)
    - Foundation News - The Foundation Trustee - The Journal of Philanthropy, 1973 July-Aug. (Box 34, Folder 260)
    - Wami News, 1974 Jan.-Feb. (Box 34, Folder 261)
    - AGB Reports - Association of Governing - Board of Universities and Colleges, 1974 March (Box 34, Folder 262)
    - Voluntary Transitional Cultural Exchange Organizations of the U.S. - A Selected List - Center for Voluntary Society, 1974 April (Box 35, Folder 263)
    - Foundation News - Prudence and Creativity - A Trustee Responsibilty - The Journal of Philanthropy, 1974 May-June (Box 35, Folder 264)
    - Federal Health Spending 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 265)
    - The Honors Program in Medical Education - At Northwestern University 1961-1976, 1977 Aug. (Box 35, Folder 266)
    - Health and the War on Poverty - A Ten Year Apprasial, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 267)
    - Corporate Governance in America - The American Assembly, Columbia University, 1978 April 13-16 (Box 35, Folder 268)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - A Thirty-Six Year Perspective 1923-1959, 1978 Nov. (Box 35, Folder 269)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Report of the Exchange Program Between The Medical Schools of The University of Lagos and Rochester 1962-1979 (Box 35, Folder 270)
    - The Picker-Commonwealth Fund Schools Program, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 271)
    - A Commonwealth Paper - What's Being Done About Medicaid?, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 272)
    - What New Yorkers Say About Their Health Care - Presidents Essay - Reprint 1982 Annual Report of CWF, 1982 Dec. (Box 36, Folder 273)
    - A Commonwealth Paper - The Financial Condition of N.Y.C. Voluntary Hospitals, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 274)
    - The President's Report - Leaders - Reprint - 1984 Annual Report of the CWF, 1985 April (Box 36, Folder 275)
    - A Commonwealth Fund Paper - The Health Sector - Its Significance for the Economy of New York City, 1985 Aug. (Box 36, Folder 276)
    - A Commonwealth Fund Paper - The Financial Condition of New York City - Voluntary Hospitals - II, 1985 Sept. (Box 36, Folder 277)
    - What New Yorkers Say About Their Health Care - Study No. 844010 - Field Work, 1985 June-Oct. (Box 36, Folder 278)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Career Beginnings Program, 1986 Jan. (Box 36, Folder 279)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Sample Media Coverage of Selected Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 280)
    - Picker/ Commonwealth Quality of Care and Managed Care Program - Health Care Coverage and Access Program - Program Summaries, 1986 March (Box 36, Folder 281)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Sample Media Coverage of Selected Programs, 1986 April-June (Box 36, Folder 282, Folder 283)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - The Career Beginnings Program - Selected Clippings, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 284)
    - The Uninsured and Uncompensated Care - A Chart Book, 1986 June (Box 36, Folder 285)
    - A Commonwealth Fund Source Book - The Validity and Value of Health Survey Research by Telephone, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 286)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Media Coverage of Louis Harris Poll Conducted for the CWF - Commission on Elderly People Living Alone, 1987 Jan. (Box 37, Folder 288)
    - Harkness House - Pamphlet, 1987 Feb. (Box 37, Folder 289)
    - Old, Alone and Poor - A Plan for Reducing Poverty Among Elderly People Living Alone - Overview and Recommendations, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 290)
    - Old, Alone and Poor - A Plan for Reducing Poverty Among Elderly People Living Alone - Overview and Recommendations, 1987 April 16 (Box 37, Folder 291)
    - The Grants Management Program - Reprint - 1985 Annual Report of the CWF, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 292)
    - A Commonwealth Fund Paper - Teenaged Mothers Seventeen Years Later, 1987 Aug. (Box 37, Folder 293)
    - A Commonwealth Fund Paper - What to do About the Nursing Shortage, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 294)
    - Enabling Older Americans to Work - Reprint - 1989 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 38, Folder 295)
    - Building the Future of Geriatrics - Reprint - 1989 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 38, Folder 296)
    - Toward More Appropriate Use of Medical Care - Reprint - 1989 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 38, Folder 297)
    - Health Affairs - Summer, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 298)
    - Appropriateness of Care - A Chart Book, 1989 June (Box 38, Folder 299)
    - The Impact of Increased Employment of Older Workers on the National Economy, 1989 December (Box 38, Folder 301, Folder 300)
    - The Senior Vice President's Report on Major Programs - Reprint from 1990 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 38, Folder 302)
    - Working with Business to Improve Employment Opportunities for Older Americans - A Literature Review - Background Paper, 1990 Feb. (Box 38, Folder 303)
    - Retirement Preferences and Plans of Older American Workers - A Background Paper, 1990 Oct. (Box 38, Folder 304)
    - Career Beginnings Impact Evaluation - Findings from a Program for Disadvantaged Highh School Students - Selected Tables and Figures, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 305)
    - Career Beginnings Impact Evaluation - Findings from the Program for Disadvantaged High School Students and Executive Summary, 1990 Oct. (Box 38, Folder 306)
    - Hospitals - The Magazine for Health Care Executives, 1990 Nov. 5 (Box 38, Folder 307)
    - The Fellowship Program in Academic Medicine for Minority Students, 1990-1996 (Box 39, Folder 308)
    - Across the Board - The Conference Board Magazine, 1991 April (Box 39, Folder 309)
    - Bridge Employment and Job Stopping in the 1980's - A Background Paper, 1991 May (Box 39, Folder 310)
    - Using Retirees to fill Temporary Labor Needs - The Traveler's Experience - A Background Paper, 1991 May (Box 39, Folder 311)
    - Are Older Workers "Good Buys"? - A Case Study of Days Inns of America - A Background Paper, 1991 May (Box 39, Folder 312)
    - Life Satisfaction and Older Adults - A Background Paper, 1991 Sept. (Box 39, Folder 313)
    - The Human Resource Potential of Americans Over 50 - Human Resource Management, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 314)
    - Relation of Work and Retirement to Health and Well-Being in Older Age - Reprint from Psychology and Aging, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 315)
    - The Emerging Science of Patient Care - Reprint from 1991 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 39, Folder 316)
    - The President's Essay - Healers - Reprint from 1991 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 39, Folder 317)
    - The Senior Vice President's Report on Major Programs - Reprint from 1991 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 39, Folder 318)
    - The Trasurer's Report - Reprint from the 1991 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 39, Folder 319)
    - Grant Watch - Health Affairs - Essay - The Consumer Movement Takes Hold in Medical Care, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 320)
    - Data Watch - Health Affairs - Patients Evaluate Their Hospital Care - A National Survey - Winter, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 321)
    - Building the Future of Geriatrics Society, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 322)
    - Cost and Benefits of Hiring Older Workers - A Case Study of B & Q - International Journal of Manpower, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 323)
    - The Impact of Future Demographic Shifts on the Employment of Older Workers - Human Resource Management, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 324)
    - A Five-Nation Perspective on the Elderly - Reprint from Health Affairs, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 325)
    - Are Older Workers "Good Buy"? - A Case Study of Days Inns of America, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 326)
    - Meeting the Medical Needs of the Senior Boom, 1992 April (Box 40, Folder 327)
    - Executive Nurse Fellowship Program - Pamphlet, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 328)
    - The President's Essay - Innovations - Reprint From 1993 Annual Report of the CWF (Box 40, Folder 329)
    - The Executive Vice President's Report on Major Programs - Reprint from 1993 Annual Reort of the CWF (Box 40, Folder 330)
    - For the Common Good - The Commonwealth Fund 1918-1993 (Box 40, Folder 331)
    - Assessing and Improving Women's Health - The Women's Research and Education Institute, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - Droping Out of High School - A Pilot Survey of Young African American Males in Four Cities, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 333)
    - Fourteen Years of Creative Leadership - Tribute to Margaret E. Mahoney, 1980-1994 (Box 40, Folder 334)
    - Grantwatch - Health Affairs - Essay - Managed Care - Promise and Concerns - Fall, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 335)
    - Universal Coverage - Building on Medicare and Employer Financing - Reprint from Health Affairs 1994 (Box 40, Folder 336)
    - Seniors In National and Community Service - A Report Prepared for the Commonwealth Fund's Americans Over 55 Work Program, 1994 April (Box 40, Folder 337)
    - Health Affairs - The Policy Journal of the Health Sphere Mandates - The Road to Reform Vol. 13 No. 2, Spring II, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 338)
    - Breast and Cervical Cancer Screening - Program for Underserved Women, 1994 July (Box 40, Folder 339, Folder 340)
    - Health Care Reform - What is at Stake for Women?, 1994 July (Box 41, Folder 341)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Recent Grants Awarded by the Board of Directors, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 342)
    - Mini-White House Conference on Aging - On Expanding Employment Opportunities for Older Americans, 1995 Feb. 7-8 (Box 41, Folder 343)
    - Medicare Turns Thirty - Excerpts from Senate Finance Committee Testimony, 1995 Feb. 7-8 (Box 41, Folder 344)
    - Women and Mental Health - Issues for Health Reform - Background Paper, 1995 March (Box 41, Folder 345)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Board of Directors Retreat - Briefing Material, 1994 July 13-15 (Box 41, Folder 347, Folder 346)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Survey of Physician Experiences with Managed Care, 1995 July-Nov. (Box 41, Folder 348)
    - Recent Grants of the Commonwealth Fund Awards by the Board of Directors, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 349)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in Tennessee - Kaiser/ Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Program and Update, 1995 July, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 351, Box 41, Folder 350)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Quarterly - A Digest of Current Work in Health Policy and Practice, 1995-1999 (Box 42, Folder 352)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - 1996 Annual report (Box 42, Folder 353)
    - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Understanding the Social Mission of Academic Health Centers, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 354)
    - The Genesis Report - Managed Care Strategic Briefing, 1996 Feb. (Box 42, Folder 355)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in California - Kaiser/Commonwealth Fund, 1996 May (Box 42, Folder 357, Folder 356)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in California - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1996 May (Box 42, Folder 359, Folder 358)
    - Bettering the Health of Minority Americans - Program Summary, 1996 June (Box 42, Folder 360)
    - Board of Directors Retreat - Briefing Material, 1996 July 12-14 (Box 42, Folder 361)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Survey of Parents with Young Childern, 1996 Aug. (Box 42, Folder 362)
    - Prevention and Women's Health - A Shared Responsibility - Policy Report, 1996 Sept. (Box 43, Folder 363)
    - Public Hospitals - A Prescription for Survival, 1996 Oct. (Box 43, Folder 364)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in New York - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1996 Oct. (Box 43, Folder 365)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in New York - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1996 Oct. (Box 43, Folder 366)
    - Program on Women's Health - Program Summary, 1996 Nov. (Box 43, Folder 367)
    - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - The Initial Effects of Tenncare on Academic Health Centers, 1996 Nov. (Box 43, Folder 368)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Restructuring Medicare's Cost-Sharing, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 369)
    - Long-Term Care for the Elderly - A Chart Book, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 370)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children - Program Summary, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 371)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Protecting Low-Income Medicare Beneficiaries, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 372)
    - Medicaid and Long-Term Care for the Elderly - Implications of Restucturing & Briefing Notes, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 373)
    - Assuring Nursing Home Quality - The History and Impact of Federal Standards in OBRA - 1987, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 374)
    - Long-Term Care for the Elderly - Chart Book, 1996 Dec. (Box 43, Folder 375)
    - Medicaid Managed Care - Lessons From Five States - Reprint from Health Affairs Vol. 15, No. 3 (Fall1996) (Box 43, Folder 376)
    - Healthy Steps - Child Health and Development Record, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 377)
    - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Understanding the Social Mission of Academic Health Centers, 1997 Jan. (Box 43, Folder 378)
    - Improving the Delivery of Cinical Preventive Services to Women in Managed Care Organizations - A Case Study Analysis, 1997 Jan. (Box 43, Folder 379)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in Florida - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1997 Jan. (Box 44, Folder 381, Box 43, Folder 380)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in Oregon - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1997 Jan. (Box 44, Folder 382)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in Tennessee - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1997 January (Box 44, Folder 383)
    - Managed Reform - Assuring Health and Economic Security for Beneficiaries - Testimony - United States Senate & Briefing Note, 1997 Jan. 23 (Box 44, Folder 384)
    - The Health of Women in the United States - Gender Differences and Gender-Specific Conditions, 1997 Feb. (Box 44, Folder 386, Folder 385)
    - Meeting the Health Need of American Children, 1997 Feb. (Box 44, Folder 387)
    - Medicare Budget Saving - Are on the Right Course for the Long-Term? Testimony - Ways and Means Committee, 1997 Feb. 13 (Box 44, Folder 388)
    - Uninsured Older Adults - Implications for Changing Medicare Eligibility with Briefing Note and Media Coverage, 1997 Feb.-March (Box 44, Folder 389)
    - Uninsured Older Adults - Implications for Changing Medicare Eligibility - 2 Copies, 1997 Feb. (Box 44, Folder 390)
    - Commonwealth Fund 1997 Album, 1997 Feb., May, June (Box 44, Folder 391)
    - Selected Facts on U. S. Women's Health - nChart Book, 1997 March (Box 44, Folder 393, Folder 392)
    - Medicare - Options for the Long-Term Changes, 1997 March 6 (Box 44, Folder 395, Folder 394)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - A Case Study of Managed Care in Texes - Kaiser/ Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project, 1997 March (Box 44, Folder 396, Folder 397)
    - Care for the Uninsured and Underinsured in the Age of Managed Care & Briefing Note, 1997 March (Box 45, Folder 399, Folder 398)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Survey of Physician Experiences with Managed Care & Briefing Note, 1997 March (Box 45, Folder 400)
    - Case Studies of Women's Health Centers - Innovations and Issues in Women - Centered Care, 1997 March (Box 45, Folder 401)
    - Executive Summary - Key Issues Affecting Accssibility to Medicap Insurance, 1997 March-April (Box 45, Folder 402)
    - Hospital Conversion Trends - Reprint - Health Affairs & Briefing Note, 1997 March-April (Box 45, Folder 404, Folder 403)
    - Risk Adjustment is not Enough - Stastegies to Limit Risk Selection in the Medicare Program & Briefing Note, 1997 April (Box 45, Folder 406, Folder 405)
    - Risk Adjustment and Medicare & Briefing Note, 1997 April (Box 45, Folder 407)
    - Risk Adjustment and Medicare, 1997 April (Box 45, Folder 408)
    - Putting Healthy Steps into Practice - Healthy Steps Training Manual, 1997 April (Box 45, Folder 409)
    - Task Force on Academic Centers - Program Summary & Briefing Note, 1997 April (Box 45, Folder 410)
    - Alternatives - News Letter of the Center for Policy Alternatives Vol. 5, No. 4, 1997 April-May (Box 45, Folder 411)
    - Alliance for Health Reform - Briefing, 1997 April, June-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 412)
    - New York Academy of Medicine - MEM Symposium - State of the Nations Health, 1997 May 12 (Box 45, Folder 413)
    - Archives of Pathology & Laboratory Medicine, 1997 May 14 (Box 45, Folder 414)
    - Leveling the Playing Field - Financing the Missions of Academic Health Centers, 1997 May (Box 45, Folder 415)
    - Reining in the Growth in Home Health Services Under Medicare & Briefing Note, 1997 May (Box 45, Folder 417, Folder 416)
    - Medicare - A Success in Improving Health Care for Older Americans, 1997 May 29 (Box 45, Folder 418)
    - Managed Care and Low-Income Populations - Side-By-Side Comparisons of State Initiatives - Kaiser/Commonwealth Low-Income Coverage and Access Project & Briefing Note, 1997 June-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 419)
    - Report of the Finance Committee and the Treasurer of the Board of Directors of the CWF, 1997 July 10 (Box 45, Folder 420)
    - The Park Council - Executive Summary - Park Survey, 1997 July-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 421)
    - Key Issues Affecting Accessibility to Medigap Insurance with Briefing Note and Media Coverage, 1997 Aug. (Box 46, Folder 422)
    - Key Issues Affecting Accessibility to Medigap Insurance, 1997 Aug. (Box 46, Folder 423)